<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Meals On Wheels</string>


    //Headings
    <string name="heading_one_a">Zero</string>
    <string name="heading_one_b">Community</string>
    <string name="heading_one_c">Meals On Wheels</string>
    <string name="heading_two_a">Food Wastage</string>
    <string name="heading_two_b">Kitchen</string>
    <string name="heading_two_c">India</string>


    //Description
    <string name="desc_one">Not to waste our basic need, food and helping communities to grow together.</string>
    <string name="desc_two">Cooking Food everyday and serving it to ensure the Health Index doesn\'t go low for India.</string>
    <string name="desc_three">Ensuring no stomach would stay hungry at Hospitals and Railway platforms.</string>

    //About Us Text

    <string name="about_us_first"> BDF envisages an inclusive and nurturing society and seeks to achieve this by developing and implementing innovative social welfare programmes which have a lasting positive impact on the lives of the most vulnerable populations. Our dream is to build a new India where people have the power to create opportunities for themselves and their communities.
Our goal is to empower people and transform their lives by providing them with food, education, healthcare, and other resources essential to their livelihood.</string>

    <string name="about_us_second">"Helping People To Help Themselves Grow" is the abiding motto of BDF.</string>

    <string name="about_us_third">Since its inception, BDF has taken an initiative to enroll 35 dropout students in government schools under our "Back To School Program."
        234 hunger drives have been conducted, whereby 7,00,000 free meals were distributed, reaching over 37,000 people.
        The effort has been possible by way of collection of surplus food from celebrations or functions and accepting food grain donations from a mindful givers and generous donors.
        Work through collection of surplus food from celebrations or functions, accepting food grain donations from our mindful givers and heartful donors.
        We also conduct Happiness Drives where people celebrate their birthdays with children for a cause. In this way, we try to ensure that nobody, particularly children, do not go to bed hungry.</string>


</resources>